hi everybody welcome to jimmy dore show
we have special guest it's John Kiriakou
who's a columnist for reader supported
news he was a CIA operations officer
until he blew the whistle on the CIA for
its use of waterboarding and he now
hosts the show co-host a show loud and
clear on Sputnik radio please welcome
back whistleblower John Kiriakou hey
John hey so Jonah we have you on I
wanted to get your expert opinion on the
way the FBI investigated the DNC server
now I've said on this show since forever
since 2016 that we'll never know who
hacked into the DNC server because the
DNC did not allow the Department of
Homeland Security nor the FBI to inspect
their server and right and so a lot of
people in the last sold in the last two
or three weeks there's been a big
propaganda push to try to discredit
people who are saying the truth which is
what I'm saying is that the FBI never
inspected the DNC servers and now
somehow that's all okay because who
knows why it's okay
hey how about the next time I commit a
crime I can hire my own private
investigator and I can just give my
findings over to the FBI
so here's the article that so this guy
tweet so this happens a lot so this guy
tweets this at me and I'll tell you what
he says he says Jimmy Dore here is the
info on the DNC server that you say you
haven't seen the president can spout
conspiracy theories all he wants but the
DNC turned over all its key data to the
FBI after it got hacked and that info
wasn't stored on a single server so he
links to this article from The Daily
Beast which is a real reputable
organization who has Chelsea Clinton on
their board and and wrote I don't know
about 10 tons worth a garbage
during the 2016 election about Bernie
Sanders and progressive so now they're
telling you the truth so if you read
this article people keep pointing me to
this article and it shows you that the
DNC did not in fact give the FBI access
but that's all okay now because they
gave them a
copy a picture and that's just as good
as anything as a forensic and it's
supposed to be okay everything's
supposed to be okay and if you don't
believe what this article says in The
Daily Beast you're some kind of a
poisonous idiot traitor even in this
article this article durst showing you
as proof it says this quote at the same
hearing Comey complained that the DNC
didn't give the FBI direct ask access to
the DNC servers that's from that exact
article that people keep referencing
that it's okay that that the FBI didn't
get it it's not okay that the FBI didn't
get and there's a thing called well John
let me ask you to explain it because
William Binney sent me an email William
Binney who's also from VIPs veterans
intelligence professionals for sanity
who debunked the weapons of mass
destruction bill Binney who invented
thin thread so bailed bin belly the
smartest guy ever work at the NSA he
sent me an email and said that this
breaks the chain of custody John can you
talk to me about that it does break the
chain of custody and as such the
information once it finally ends up at
the FBI is useless information and can't
be used in an investigation or a court
of law
the chain of custody is that that the
the evidence the information that's
gathered has to immediately go from its
point of origin to a law enforcement
official and it has to remain with law
enforcement until it's turned over to
the Justice Department for final
disposition whether it's prosecution or
further investigation or whatever and
this was not this did not go directly to
the FBI a copy went to the FBI and you
know one of the things about that
article to Jimmy was that they kept
using the word forensic like they're
trying to convince everybody he just
with the word forensic somehow
official and it was okay and we should
take their word for it either of these
governmental agencies telling us to take
their word for it let me say something
too about Bill Binney bill Binney is a
good friend of mine I have never met
anybody as brilliant when it comes to
electronics as bill Binney he's one of
this country's leading thinkers on
issues of Internet privacy and
Benni proved that the information could
not have been hacked remotely because of
the speed at which the information was
stolen
he said the speed indicated that the
information was downloaded onto a thumb
drive which means that the person who
did it was there inside the dnc that
person was the whistleblower now if we
don't know who that was we could
speculate but we really don't know who
it was but the bottom line is that this
narrative that The Daily Beast and
others on the Left are pushing on us is
just simply incorrect it's just a
propaganda it is it is and and and and
you know what I'm not smarter than I'm
sure I'm not smarter than the guy who
wrote that article and I'm not smarter
than James Comey and I'm not smarter
than you know whoever at The Daily Beast
but you don't need to be smart to see
through that that's that's why
I know it's because I see
through it and if someone as dumb as me
can see through it in your own goddamn
article you have the FBI chief saying
they wanted to have access to the
servers and you denied it to
them and you hired it for a third party
since when do we get to hire third
parties and when we think something
we've had an attack on our country
because that's what people are couching
this as this is cypresses warfare and
where we put sanctions on Russia over
this for F sake you're gonna let us some
third party investigate this
that's why I know that's and it
gets the CC K and I'll show you one more
thing this is from a year ago
Michael senado wrote this article and
counterpunch the headline is
cybersecurity firm that attributed DNC
acts to Russia may have fabricated
Russia hacking in Ukraine huh wait a
minute so here's this I'll show you this
it says the cyber security firm
outsource by the Democratic National
Committee CrowdStrike reportedly misread
data falsely attributing a hacking in
Ukraine to the Russians in December 2016
this is after our election they did this
voice of America a US government funded
media outlet reported quote the
CrowdStrike report released in December
asserted that russians hacked into a
ukraine artillery app
resulting in heavy losses of howitzers
and Ukraine's war with Russia backed
separatists but the International
Institute for Strategic Studies told VOA
that CrowdStrike erroneously used a ISS
data as proof of an intrusion I ISS
disavowed any connection to the
CrowdStrike report and ears more
Ukraine's Ministry of Defense also
claimed combat losses and hacking never
occurred the maker of the military app
allegedly hacked called crowd strikes
report delusional and told fo a that
crowd strike never contacted him either
before or after they completed their
report VOA news noted Ukraine's
rebuttal to crowd strike received little
media attention as crowd strikes report
was widely cited in media outlets
throughout the United States as further
evidence of Russia hacking in the United
States get this the firm ci CTO and
co-founder dmitriyevich is a senior
fellow at the Atlantic Council a think
tank with openly anti-russian sentiments
that is funded by who a ukrainian
billionaire viktor Pinchuk who also
happened to donate ten million dollars
to the clinton foundation
so there's your goddamn crowd strike
with your Daily Beast article it sucks
it's empty it's propaganda on its face
and I see right through it and you can
all keep pushing your stupid propaganda
and becoming establishment mouthpieces
because it works for you but I Got News
for you nobody else buys it outside your
stupid bubble less than 1% of the
country thinks Russia is a problem this
isn't working so what do you make of
that report that's from a year ago
John I'm with you a hundred percent I've
never believed this narrative there's
never been any proof there's never been
anything beyond somebody's analysis and
you know again I'm going to come back to
the CIA and to the FBI when they don't
offer up evidence and they say
take our word for it that's when you
should run in the opposite direction and
that's what we've had from the very
beginning on this issue is the likes of
John Brennan and Jim clapper and Mike
Hayden and others saying take our word
for it no thanks the last time we took
your word for it
we ended up in a war that we still
haven't gotten out of that's right
that's right so okay so they're there
that's my response to everybody who
keeps telling me I need to read this
daily beast report you need to get your
head out of your ass and stop believing
the intelligence community and trust you
don't so that's the beauty of democracy
it's not based on trust it's based on
mistrust which is why we were supposed
to have transparency which is why when
John F Kennedy was dealing with the
Cuban Missile Crisis he made top-secret
aerial photos available to the United
States people okay cuz democracy's based
on mistrust and transparency well John
thanks for being our guest I really
appreciate it
work as much thanks for having me where
can people find you let's see I'm at
Sputnik news.com you can go to loud and
clear we're also on I heart radio and
iTunes and let's see Facebook Twitter
John Kiriakou calm I'm all over the
place like dog poo thanks for watching
please make sure you're subscribed even
if you think you are you're probably not
it only takes a second to check and then
you have to ring that Bell so they send
you a notification when we drop a new
video otherwise they won't tell you when
we drop new videos and if you like our
show please help support it become a
patron we give you hours of bonus
material every week and we give a live
stream we do a live stream every
Saturday at 2:00 p.m. Pacific time when
you could ask us questions and we answer
them back thanks for your support
you